RG 002:004, General Assembly Papers
Connecticut State Library
General Assembly papers
1871-2010
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly
948.75 cubic feet
The General Assembly Papers begin in the year 1803 and continue through 2010. The papers described here cover the years 1871-2010. They consist of official papers that document the activities of the General Assembly such as petitions, appointments, proclamations, resolutions, amendments, committee reports, Public and Special Acts, rejected bills, and unfinished business.
RG002_004b
Multiple
Scope and Content
The General Assembly Papers begin in the year 1803 and continue through 2010. The papers described here cover the years 1871-2010. They consist of official papers that document the activities of the General Assembly such as petitions, appointments, proclamations, resolutions, amendments, committee reports, Public and Special Acts, rejected bills, and unfinished business. Public and Special Acts begin in 1880. Rejected bills and unfinished business both begin in 1913.
Arrangement
The General Assembly Papers are arranged chronologically by year and then by type of document. For the years 1882-1883 and after 1907, Public and Special Acts are chronological by act number within the year. Rejected bills are alphabetical by committee between 1913-1961. Beginning in 1947, unfinished business is alphabetical by committee.
Related Material
, Connecticut State Library.
, Connecticut State Library.
, Connecticut State Library.
, Connecticut State Library.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. General Assembly
Subjects:
Bills, legislative -- Connecticut; Connecticut -- Politics and government
Document Types:
Bills (legislative records); Petitions; Reports
Restrictions on Access
Years 1871-1911, which is accession T003307, are stored onsite. All years after 1911 are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Custodial History
The General Assembly submitted these records to the Office of the Secretary of the State, which subsequently transferred them to the Connecticut State Library. For records after the years listed here contact the Office of the Secretary of the State.
Container List
- 1871-1911, T003307; Boxes 52-78 are unprocessed. Materials are arranged chronologically by year, but the contents of each box are not organized.; Boxes 1-25 are processed. There is no box 8. The materials are arranged chronologically and by type of document.
  - 1871
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 106)
    - Report of the Insurance Commission (Box 106)
    - Report on the necessity of an Inebriate Asylum (Box 106)
    - Appointments (Box 106)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 107)
    - Sheffield Scientific School report (Box 107)
    - Report of the General Hospital for the Insane (Box 107)
    - Report of the Fitch Home for Soldiers (Box 107)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 108)
    - Report of the Canvasser for Votes on Governor, members of Congress, State Officers (Box 108)
    - Report of the State Librarian on births, marriages and deaths in Connecticut, 1870 (Box 108)
    - Report of the School Fund (Box 108)
    - Report of the Committee on Humane Institutions (Box 108)
  - 1872
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 109)
    - Appointments (Box 109)
    - The Report of the Fish Commissioner (Box 109)
    - Report of the Traveler's Insurance Corporation (Box 109)
    - Report of the Charter Oak Fire Insurance Company (Box 109)
    - Report of the School Fund (Box 109)
    - Report of the Surveyor General (Box 109)
    - Report of the Board of Education (Box 109)
    - Report of the Sheffield Scientific School (Box 109)
    - Report to determine the correctness of statements made by Mutual Fire Insurance Company (Box 109)
    - Report of the State Librarian concerning births, deaths, and marriages in Connecticut (Box 109)
    - Report of the Bridgeport Horse Railroad Company (Box 109)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 110)
    - Report of the Bank Commission (Box 110)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 111)
    - Canvasser's report on votes for Comptroller (Box 111)
    - Canvasser's report on votes for Sheriff (Box 111)
  - 1872-1873
    - Report of the Bridgeport Horse Railroad Company (Box 111)
  - 1873
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 111)
    - Report of the Board of Education (Box 111)
    - Report of the Adjutant General (Box 111)
    - Report of the State Librarian on births, marriages and deaths in Connecticut (Box 111)
    - Report of the Fish Commissioner (Box 111)
    - Report of the School Fund (Box 111)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 112)
    - Appointments (Box 112)
    - Canvassing for votes for Governors (Box 112)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 113)
    - 71st annual report of the Conn. State Reform School (Box 113)
    - Report of the Conn. Industrial School for Girls (Box 113)
    - Report of the Conn. Soldiers Orphans Home (Box 113)
    - Report of the Bridgeport Protestant Widows Relief Society (Box 113)
    - Report of the Trustees of Fitch's Home at Darien (Box 113)
    - Report of the Conn. School for Imbeciles (Box 113)
    - Report of the Bank Commission (Box 113)
    - Report of the Adjutant General (Box 113)
    - Report of the State Librarian on registration of births, marriages, deaths and divorces (Box 117)
  - 1873-1875
    - Report of the Committee on State Board of Health and Vital Statistics (Box 117)
    - Report of the Superintendent to the Trustees of the State Reform School (Box 117)
    - State Resolutions on the Federal Interference in the affairs of the State of Louisiana (Box 117)
  - 1874
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 114)
    - Appointments (Box 114)
    - An act relative to the city of Bridgeport (Box 115)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 116)
    - Report of the Connecticut State Prison (Box 116)
    - Report of the Bank Commission (Box 116)
    - Report of the State Board of Education (Box 116)
    - Report of the Norwalk Horse Railway (Box 116)
    - Report of the New Haven-Centerville Horse Railway (Box 116)
    - Report of the State Street Horse Railway (Box 116)
    - Report of the Connecticut School for Imbeciles (Box 116)
    - Report of the Connecticut Hospital for the Insane (Box 116)
    - Report of the School Fund Commission (Box 116)
    - Canvasser's report on votes (Box 117)
  - 1874-1875
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 117)
  - 1875
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 115)
    - Special reports of the Insurance Commission; National Life and Trust Company of New Haven (Box 115)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 118)
    - Report of the Connecticut School for Imbeciles (Box 118)
    - Report of the Commissioner of the School Fund (Box 118)
    - Report of the Fish Commissioners (Box 118)
    - Report of the Connecticut State Prison (Box 118)
    - Report of the Board of Education (Box 118)
    - Report concerning pauper legislation (Box 118)
    - Report of the Committee on Penal Treatment of Inebriates (Box 118)
    - Report of the Connecticut Industrial School for Girls (Box 118)
    - Report of the Connecticut Hospital for the Insane (Box 118)
    - Report of the Connecticut Soldiers Orphans Home (Box 118)
    - Report of the State Librarian on registration of births, marriages, deaths, and divorces (Box 118)
    - Register of the grand list, 1875 October (Box 122)
  - 1875-1877
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 119)
    - Report of the Board of Education (Box 119)
    - Report of the Commissioners of the School Fund (Box 119)
    - Report of the Insurance Commissioner (Box 119)
    - Report of the Railroad Commissioners (Box 119)
    - Report of the Connecticut Industrial School for Girls (Box 119)
  - 1876
    - Report of the State Librarian on births, marriages, deaths, and divorces (Box 119)
    - Report of the Connecticut School for Imbeciles (Box 119)
    - Register of the grand list, 1876 October (Box 122)
  - 1876-1877
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 120)
    - Report of the State Canvassers (Box 120)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 121)
  - 1877
    - Report of the State Librarian on the registration of births, marriages, deaths, and divorces (Box 121)
    - Report of the Bank Commissioners (Box 121)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 122)
    - Report of the Connecticut School for Imbeciles (Box 122)
    - Report of the Connecticut Hospital for the Insane (Box 122)
    - Report of the Commissioner of the School Fund (Box 122)
    - Report of the Treasurer of Yale College report of the Governor's Special Committee on Charitable Institutions (Box 122)
    - Report of the Board of Education (Box 122)
    - Report of the State Canvassers (Box 122)
    - Report of the Treasurer (Box 122)
    - Report of the Comptroller of Public Accounts for fiscal year ending november 30, 1877 (Box 122)
    - Register of the grand list, 1877 October (Box 127)
  - 1877-1878
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 123)
    - Report of the Connecticut State Reform School (Box 123)
    - Charter of the borough of Birmingham (Box 123)
  - 1878
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 124)
    - Report of the Connecticut Hospital for the Insane (Box 124)
    - Report of the Special Commission on Life Insurance (Box 124)
    - Report of the State Treasurer (Box 124)
    - Report of the Fish Commissioner (Box 124)
    - Special Report of the Insurance Commissioner (Box 124)
    - Reports of the State Capitol Commissioner (Box 124)
    - Report relating to the establishment of a navy yard on the Thames River (Box 124)
    - Report of the School Fund Commissioner (Box 124)
    - Report of the Bank Commissioner (Box 124)
    - Report of the Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 125)
    - Report of the Special Commission on life insurance companies on, Aetna, Traveler's and other companies (Box 125)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 125)
    - Report of the Comptroller of Public Accounts for fiscal year ending november 30, 1878 (Box 127)
    - Register of the grand list, 1878 October (Box 127)
  - 1878-1879
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 126)
    - Report of the Commissioners of Laws relating to insurance acts relating to Insurance Companies (Box 126)
  - 1879
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 127)
    - Report of the Fish Commissioners (Box 127)
    - Report of the Bank Commissioners (Box 127)
    - Treasurer's report, 1879 January (Box 127)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 128)
    - Reports of the State Board of Health (Box 128)
    - Reports of the town electors of the State of Conn. on votes for State Senators (Box 128)
    - Report of the Railroad Commissioners (Box 128)
    - Report of the Comptroller on the new State Capitol (Box 128)
    - Report of the Board of State House Commissioners and appendix (Box 128)
    - Report of the Commissioners on the insane asylum at Middletown (Box 128)
    - Report of the Conn. Industrial School for Girls (Box 128)
    - Resolution to amend the charter of the borough of Bethel (Box 128)
    - Resolution consolidating and amending the charter of the borough of Stanford (Box 128)
    - An act revising and amending the charter of the city of Meriden (Box 128)
    - Report of the Committee on Usurpation of Power by the Federal Judiciary in Virginia (Box 129)
    - Report of the Commissioner of the School Fund (Box 129)
    - Report of the Board of Education (Box 129)
  - 1879-1880
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 129)
  - 1880
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 130-131)
    - An act annulling the corporate existence of certain Joint-Stock Companies (Box 131)
    - Final report of the State Capitol Commissioners (Box 131)
    - Petitions and Resolutions (Box 132)
    - Report of the Special Commission on contract convict labor (Box 132)
    - Report of the Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 132)
    - Report of the Directors of the Connecticut State Prison (Box 132)
    - Report of the Bank Commissioners (Box 132)
    - Report of the Fish Commissioner (Box 132)
    - Report of the Railroad Commissioners (Box 132)
    - Report of the Commissioner of the School Fund (Box 132)
    - Report of the Governor's Select Board of Commissioners on revising the Joint Stock Laws (Box 132)
  - 1880-1881
    - Reports, Public Acts (Box 133)
  - 1881
    - Public and Special Acts (Box 134-135)
    - Public and Special Acts, Reports (Box 136)
    - Special Acts, Reports, Appointments (Box 137)
  - 1882
    - Public Acts, 1-50 (Box 138)
    - Public Acts, 51-148 (Box 139)
    - Special Acts, 1-80 (Box 140)
    - Special Acts, 81-150 (Box 141)
    - Special Acts, 151-215 (Box 142)
    - Reports (Box 144)
    - Reports, Appointments, Commissions (Box 145)
  - 1883
    - Special Acts, 216-248 (Box 143)
    - Public Acts, 1-100 (Box 146)
    - Public Acts, 101-137 (Box 147)
    - Special Acts, 1-80 (Box 148)
    - Special Acts, 81-140 (Box 149)
    - Special Acts, 141-204 (Box 150)
    - Appointments, Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 151)
    - Reports (Box 152)
  - 1883-1884
    - Public Acts (Box 53)
    - Special Acts (Box 53)
    - Proclamations (Box 53)
    - Appointments (Box 53)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 53)
    - Reports (Box 53)
  - 1884-1885
    - Public Acts (Box 54)
    - Special Acts (Box 54)
    - Proclamations (Box 54)
    - Appointments (Box 54)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 54)
    - Reports (Box 54)
  - 1885-1886
    - Public Acts (Box 55)
    - Special Acts (Box 55)
    - Proclamations (Box 55)
    - Appointments (Box 55)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 55)
    - Reports (Box 55)
  - 1886
    - Reports (Box 55A)
  - 1886-1887
    - Public Acts (Box 56)
    - Special Acts (Box 56)
    - Proclamations (Box 56)
    - Appointments (Box 56)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 56)
    - Reports (Box 56)
  - 1887
    - Public Acts (Box 57)
    - Special Acts (Box 57)
    - Proclamations (Box 57)
    - Appointments (Box 57)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 57)
    - Reports (Box 57)
  - 1887-1889
    - Public Acts (Box 52)
    - Special Acts (Box 52)
    - Proclamations (Box 52)
    - Appointments (Box 52)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 52)
    - Reports (Box 52)
  - 1889
    - Public Acts (Box 58-59)
    - Special Acts (Box 58-59)
    - Proclamations (Box 58-59)
    - Appointments (Box 58-59)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 58-59)
    - Reports (Box 58-59)
  - 1889-1893
    - Public Acts (Box 60)
    - Special Acts (Box 60)
    - Proclamations (Box 60)
    - Appointments (Box 60)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 60)
  - 1893
    - Public Acts (Box 61-62)
    - Special Acts (Box 61-62)
    - Proclamations (Box 61-62)
    - Appointments (Box 61-62)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 61-62)
    - Reports (Box 61-62)
  - 1893-1895
    - Public Acts (Box 63)
    - Special Acts (Box 63)
    - Proclamations (Box 63)
    - Appointments (Box 63)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 63)
    - Reports (Box 63)
  - 1895
    - Public Acts (Box 65-66)
    - Special Acts (Box 65-66)
    - Proclamations (Box 65-66)
    - Appointments (Box 65-66)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 65-66)
    - Reports (Box 65-66)
  - 1895-1897
    - Public Acts (Box 67)
    - Special Acts (Box 67)
    - Proclamations (Box 67)
    - Appointments (Box 67)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 67)
    - Reports (Box 67)
  - 1897
    - Public Acts (Box 68-69)
    - Special Acts (Box 68-69)
    - Proclamations (Box 68-69)
    - Appointments (Box 68-69)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 68-69)
    - Reports (Box 68-69)
  - 1899
    - Public Acts (Box 70-71)
    - Special Acts (Box 70-71)
    - Proclamations (Box 70-71)
    - Appointments (Box 70-71)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 70-71)
  - 1889-1901
    - Public Acts (Box 72)
    - Special Acts (Box 72)
    - Proclamations (Box 72)
    - Appointments (Box 72)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 72)
    - Reports (Box 72)
  - 1901
    - Public Acts (Box 73)
    - Special Acts (Box 73)
    - Proclamations (Box 73)
    - Appointments (Box 73)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 73)
    - Reports (Box 73)
  - 1901-1903
    - Public Acts (Box 74)
    - Special Acts (Box 74)
    - Proclamations (Box 74)
    - Appointments (Box 74)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 74)
    - Reports (Box 74)
  - 1903
    - Public Acts (Box 75-76)
    - Special Acts (Box 75-76)
    - Proclamations (Box 75-76)
    - Appointments (Box 75-76)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 75-76)
    - Reports (Box 75-76)
  - 1905
    - Public Acts (Box 77)
    - Special Acts (Box 77)
    - Proclamations (Box 77)
    - Appointments (Box 77)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 77)
    - Reports (Box 77)
  - 1905-1906
    - Public Acts (Box 78)
    - Special Acts (Box 78)
    - Proclamations (Box 78)
    - Appointments (Box 78)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 78)
    - Reports (Box 78)
  - 1907
    - Special Acts, 1-186 (Box 1)
    - Special Acts, 187-329 (Box 2)
    - Special Acts, 330-444 (Box 3)
    - Special Acts, 445-514 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 1-179 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 180-268 (Box 6)
    - Petitions and Resolutions, Annual Reports and Appointments (Box 7)
  - 1909
    - Special Acts and Engrossed Bills (Box 9-12)
    - Engrossed Bills (Box 13-14)
    - Annual Reports (Box 15)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 16)
  - 1911
    - Special Acts, 1-165 (Box 17)
    - Special Acts, 166-300 (Box 18)
    - Special Acts, 301-419 (Box 19)
    - Special Acts, 420-544 (Box 20)
    - Public Acts, 1-125 (Box 21)
    - Public Acts, 126-240 (Box 22)
    - Public Acts, 241-249 (Box 23)
    - Annual Reports (Box 24)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 25)
- 1913-1971, 1984-045
  - 1913
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions; House; Senate; Joint House; Joint Senate; Orders on the Treasury; Appointments (Box 1)
    - Public Acts, 1-138 (Box 2)
    - Public Acts, 139-241; Constitutional Amendments (Box 3)
    - Special Acts, 1-170 (Box 4)
    - Special Acts, 171-307 (Box 5)
    - Special Acts, 308-382 (Box 6)
    - Special Acts, 383-437 (Box 7)
    - Passed, but taxes not paid and not Engrossed for Governor's approval; matters not read; package from C.F. Roberts; package from John S. Addis (Box 8)
    - Disagreeing actions, January Session (Box 9)
    - Returned by Governor unsigned after adjournment (Box 9)
    - Reports to General Assembly, January Session (Box 10)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Banks; Cities and Boroughs; Claims (Box 11)
    - Rejected Bills - Constitutional Amendments; Education; Excise; Finance; Fish and Game; Humane Institutions; Incorporations; Insurance (Box 12)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 1-959 (Box 13)
    - Rejected Bills - Labor; Manual and Roll; Military Affairs; Miscellaneous; New Towns, Counties and Probate Districts; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Shell Fisheries; State Library; State Prisons; Women's Suffrage; Unfinished Business (Box 14)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions; Orders on the Treasury; Appointments; Executive General Assembly, Senate; Constitutional Amendments (Box 15)
  - 1915
    - Public Acts, 1-140 (Box 16)
    - Public Acts, 141-260 (Box 17)
    - Public Acts, 261-340 (Box 18)
    - Special Acts, 1-140 (Box 19)
    - Special Acts, 141-267 (Box 20)
    - Special Acts, 268-359 (Box 21)
    - Special Acts, 360-403 (Box 22)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Banking; Capital Furniture; Cities and Boroughs; Constitutional Amendments; Education (Box 23)
    - Rejected Bills - Excise; Federal Relations; Finance; Forfeited Rights; Humane Institutions; Incorporations; Insurance (Box 24)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 1-567 (Box 25)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 601-948; Labor; Military; New Towns and Probate Districts; Public Health and Safety; Railroads (Box 26)
    - Rejected Bills - Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Shell Fisheries; Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - 1917
    - Preliminary and Unimportant; Resolutions; House; Senate; Joint House; Joint Senate; Orders on the Treasury; Appointments; Executive General Assembly, Senate (Box 28)
    - Public Acts, 1-163 (Box 29)
    - Public Acts, 164-325 (Box 30)
    - Public Acts, 326-418 (Box 31)
    - Special Acts, 1-150 (Box 32)
    - Special Acts, 151-285 (Box 33)
    - Special Acts, 286-404 (Box 34)
    - Special Acts, 405-453 (Box 35)
  - 1918
    - Reports to the General Assembly (Box 36)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Banks; Capital Furniture; Cities and Boroughs (Box 37)
    - Rejected Bills - Claims; Constitutional Amendments; Education; Excise; Federal Relations; Finance; Fish and Game (Box 38)
    - Rejected Bills - Forfeited Rights; Human Institutions; Incorporations; Insurance; Judiciary, 8-366 (Box 39)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 367-1133 (Box 40)
    - Rejected Bills - Labor; Military Affairs; Public Health and Safety; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges (Box 41)
  - 1919
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Orders on the Treasury; Appointments; executive General Assembly - Senate (Box 42)
    - Public Acts, 1-180 (Box 43)
    - Public Acts, 181-345 (Box 44)
    - Special Acts, 1-169 (Box 45)
    - Special Acts, 170-361 (Box 46)
    - Reports to the General Assembly - Education; Finance; Human Institutions; Incorporations; Public Health and Safety; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; State Prisons (Box 47)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations (Box 48)
    - Rejected Bills - Education (Box 49)
    - Rejected Bills - Excise; Federal Relations; Finance; Fish and Game; Forfeited Rights; Human Institutions; incorporations; Insurance; Judiciary, 12-186 (Box 50)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 198-599; Labor (Box 51)
    - Rejected Bills - Military Affairs; Public Health and Safety; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Women's Suffrage; Appointments (Box 52)
  - Special Session, 1920 September 14, 21
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Public Acts; Special Acts; Reports of the General Assembly - Favorable, Unfavorable; Miscellaneous (Box 53)
  - 1921
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, Appointments; Constitutional Amendments (Box 54)
    - Public Acts, 1-175 (Box 55)
    - Public Acts, 176-298 (Box 56)
    - Public Acts, 299-404 (Box 57)
    - Special Acts, 1-160 (Box 58)
    - Special Acts, 161-276 (Box 59)
    - Special Acts, 277-352 (Box 60)
    - Special Acts, 353-482 (Box 61)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Banks; Cities and Boroughs (Box 62)
    - Rejected Bills - Cities and Boroughs; Education; Excise; Finance (Box 63)
    - Rejected Bills - Fish and Game; Federal Regulations; Forfeited Rights; Human Institutions; Incorporations; Insurance; Judiciary, 2-356 (Box 64)
    - Rejected Bills, Judiciary, 358-966 (Box 65)
    - Rejected Bills - Labor; Military Affairs; Miscellaneous; New Towns and Probate Districts; Public Health and Safety; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; State Parks; Shell Fisheries (Box 66)
    - Unfavorable Reports to the General Assembly from the Judiciary Committee (Box 67)
  - 1923
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions; Appointments; Constitutional Amendments; Reports to the General Assembly (Box 68)
    - Public Acts, 1-158 (Box 69)
    - Public Acts, 159-256 (Box 70)
    - Public Acts, 258-285 (Box 71)
    - Special Acts, 1-128 (Box 72)
    - Special Acts, 129-263 (Box 73)
    - Special Acts, 264-360 (Box 74)
    - Special Acts, 361-418 (Box 75)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Banks; Cities and Boroughs; Claims; Education (Box 76)
    - Rejected Bills - Finance; Fish and Game; Forfeited Rights; Human Institutions; Incorporations; Insurance; Judiciary, 13-236 (Box 77)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 263-942 (Box 78)